Privacy Policy of **Framework**
===============================

This Website collects some Personal Data from its Users.

Personal Data processed for the following purposes and using the following services:
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* * ### Advertising
        
        * ### Meta ads conversion tracking (Meta pixel)
            
            Personal Data: Trackers; Usage Data
            
        * ### LinkedIn conversion tracking (LinkedIn Insight Tag)
            
            Personal Data: device information; Trackers; Usage Data

    * ### Analytics
        
        * ### Google Analytics (Universal Analytics)
            
            Personal Data: Tracker; Usage Data
            
        * ### HubSpot Analytics
            
            Personal Data: Trackers; Usage Data
            
        * ### Heap Analytics
            
            Personal Data: Usage Data

    * ### Displaying content from external platforms
        
        * ### Vimeo video
            
            Personal Data: Trackers; Usage Data

    * ### Handling payments
        
        * ### Stripe
            
            Personal Data: billing address; email address; first name; last name; payment info

    * ### Handling productivity related activity
        
        * ### Google Workspace
            
            Personal Data: email address
            
        * ### Lever
            
            Personal Data: User ID

    * ### Heat mapping and session recording
        
        * ### Hotjar Heat Maps & Recordings
            
            Personal Data: Trackers; Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service

    * ### Infrastructure monitoring
        
        * ### Sentry
            
            Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service

    * ### Managing contacts and sending messages
        
        * ### Klaviyo
            
            Personal Data: email address
            
        * ### HubSpot Email
            
            Personal Data: email address; Trackers; Usage Data

    * ### Remarketing and behavioral targeting
        
        * ### Klaviyo segmentation and social advertising
            
            Personal Data: device information; email address; shopping history; Tracker; Usage Data

    * ### Tag Management
        
        * ### Segment
            
            Personal Data: Tracker; Usage Data
            
        * ### Google Tag Manager
            
            Personal Data: Usage Data

    * ### Traffic optimization and distribution
        
        * ### Cloudflare
            
            Personal Data: Tracker; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service

    * ### User database management
        
        * ### HubSpot CRM and HubSpot Lead Management
            
            Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service

Information on opting out of interest-based advertising
-------------------------------------------------------

In addition to any opt-out feature provided by any of the services listed in this document, Users may learn more on how to generally opt out of interest-based advertising within the dedicated section of the Cookie Policy.

Further information about the processing of Personal Data
---------------------------------------------------------

* * ### Further Information for Taiwan consumers
        
        1\. You agree that Framework may collect, process, save and use your personal data for reasonable use in order to provide you with other information, services or make membership statistics, or conduct surveys or research on online behavior.  
          
        2\. According to “Personal Data Protection Act” in Taiwan, you can exercise the following rights with respect to personal data：  
        Make any inquiries and requests for personal data (fees vary on a case-by-case basis).  
        Any requests to make copies of personal data (fees vary on a case-by-case basis).  
        Any request to supplement or correct personal data.  
        Any request to stop collecting, processing or using personal data.  
        Any request to delete personal data.  
          
        3\. Retention Period of Personal Data：  
        Framework will retain your personal data for the period necessary to complete the purpose of use described in this policy, unless there are statutory or other necessary circumstances, Framework will retain the data for a longer period, for instance, for customer relationship management, your personal data will be retained within an appropriate and reasonable period, or your personal data will be retained within a specific period required by law in order to comply with tax laws or other legal regulations, or to cooperate with government or judicial investigations or litigation requirements. In addition, if you agree to Framework collecting personal data from you at the beginning, but later wish to withdraw this consent, after you withdraw your consent, Framework will not continue to collect your personal data, and will only retain the personal data that Framework collected before you withdrew your consent.  
        If you request Framework to stop processing and using, or request Framework to delete your personal data. Once done, Framework will no longer be able to contact you on matters related to Framework services, keep records for future inquiries, provide you with the latest information on Framework services, or conduct a customer verification. Moreover, Framework will be unable to continue to provide services, and will not be liable for any losses caused by this.  
          
        4\. To whom Framework discloses your personal data  
        Framework will not disclose the personal data collected from you to other third parties unless any of the following circumstances applies：  
        Your consent: Framework will disclose and share your personal data with other third parties only after obtaining your consent.  
        Service provider: Framework will disclose and share the necessary items of your personal data with Framework’s service provider within the scope of the purposes mentioned in this policy, so that they can provide services to you, such as marketing companies for assisting Framework in sending marketing materials and organizing marketing activities, shipping companies for shipping your purchases or repairs, cash processors for processing payments, and customer service providers for providing customer support services for you. These service providers will use your personal data within the scope of the purposes mentioned in this policy in accordance with Framework's instructions, and Framework will ensure that they do comply with this policy.  
        Legal or protection purposes: Framework will disclose and share the necessary items of your personal data to third parties in the case of any of the following situations in order to comply with legal requirements or for preservation purposes：  
        (1) When it is necessary to comply with laws, requirements of competent authorities or judicial units, or to preserve legal requests, defenses, or to prevent fraud or investigate other illegal acts.  
        (2) To the extent permitted by law, to protect the rights, property and safety of Framework, Framework’s service providers, users or the public from being endangered.  
          
        5\. Cross-border Transfer  
        You understand and agree that when you use Framework products or services or provide your personal data to Framework, your personal data may be transferred, retained, processed, and used across borders between Framework's affiliated companies and service providers in various countries. The cross-border transfer, storage, processing and utilization behaviors mentioned above will all comply with this policy and the relevant legal requirements of individual privacy and personal data security in each country.  
          
        6\. Third Party Links and Services  
        Framework products and services may provide links to other websites, or use services provided by third parties. These third-party services are not within the control of Framework and are not covered by this privacy policy. Framework is not responsible for the privacy policies or content of such third-party services. If you have questions about how these third parties collect, use, and share your information, you are advised to review their respective privacy policies or contact the third parties directly. Linking to a third-party service through the permission of this service does not mean that Framework endorses, promotes or represents the quality of the service or assumes responsibility for its actions.  
          
        7\. If the information you provide contains any third party's personal data, you should ensure that the third party understands the rights of this policy, and ensure that you have obtained the consent of the third party and authorize Framework to use such third party's personal data in accordance with this policy.  
          
        8\. If the personal data you provide to Framework is insufficient to prove the authenticity of your identity, or if you forge your identity, steal someone else's identity or provide a false identity, Framework has the right to terminate your service.  
          
        9\. Security Measures  
        Framework will try its best to use reasonable technical and procedural protection measures to ensure the security of information collected by Framework. Framework also takes appropriate measures in accordance with relevant laws to ensure that personal data collected by third parties is always safe. However, please be aware that even if Framework takes reasonable steps to protect your information, there are no website, Internet transmission, computer system or wireless connection that can be completely secured.  
          
        10\. Privacy Rights of Minors  
        Framework will not collect personal data of minors under the age of eighteen (18) or as otherwise provided by the local laws or regulations knowingly without the consent of their parents (or guardians). Framework recommends that parents (or guardians) should accompany the minors throughout the use of Framework products and services.  
        If you are a minor, please seek the consent of your parents (or guardians). You may provide personal data to Framework only after Framework confirms that you have obtained the consent of your parents (or guardians). Your parents (or guardians) may revoke or withdraw any consent at any time.  
          
        11\. Special or Sensitive Personal Data  
        Framework will not ask you to provide Framework with special or sensitive personal data, such as your medical records, treatments, politics, religious and philosophical beliefs, race, trade union membership information, sexual orientation, sex life, criminal records or genetics.  
          
        12\. Changes to this Policy  
        When you use this website, it means that you have read, understood and agreed to accept Framework's privacy protection policy. Framework may revise the content of this policy from time to time, and you are advised to pay attention to such changes at any time.  
        If you continue to use this website after any changes, you are deemed to have read, understood and agreed to accept such changes.  
        If you do not agree with the content of this policy or its subsequent changes, or if your country or region excludes all or part of the content of the privacy protection policy, you should stop using this website immediately.  

Contact information
-------------------

* * ### Owner and Data Controller
        
        Company: Framework Computer Inc  
          
        Headquarters Address:  
        447 Sutter St  
        PMB 135  
        San Francisco, CA, 94108-4618  
        United States  
          
        Email: support@frame.work  
          
        Tel: +1 (415) 475-3769  
          
        Managing Director: Nirav Patel  
          
        UST-ID: Pending
        
        **Owner contact email:** support@frame.work

Latest update: June 20, 2024

This document has been created with the iubenda [Privacy and Cookie Policy Generator](https://www.iubenda.com/en/privacy-and-cookie-policy-generator). See also the [Terms and Conditions Generator](https://www.iubenda.com/en/terms-and-conditions-generator). [iubenda](https://www.iubenda.com/en/privacy-and-cookie-policy-generator) hosts this content and only collects [the Personal Data strictly necessary](https://www.iubenda.com/privacy-policy/65675001) for it to be provided.
